{"data":[{"question":"Biologists and anthropologists possesses a wealth of evidence to indicate that human beings arose from lower forms of life over a time long period.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"desirous ","b":"in the garden ","c":"most ","d":"other ","answer":"1","explain":"- Desirious-> desired","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"To become a skilled photograph, a person should have both manual dexterity and a good eye for detail.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"To become ","b":"photograph","c":"should have ","d":"for detail","answer":"2","explain":"- Photograph-> photographer","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"For centuries, music have played acoustical guitars, which produce sound from the vibration of the strings.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"music ","b":"which ","c":"sound ","d":"vibration ","answer":"1","explain":"- Music-> musicians","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Langston Hughes always seemed to know exactly who he was, and those knowledges helped make him one of the most respected writers in the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"exactly who ","b":"those knowledges ","c":"make him","d":"most respected ","answer":"2","explain":"- Those knowledges-> those knowledge","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Banking is ancient origin, though little 3 known about its history prior to the thirteenth century.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is ancient ","b":"though little ","c":"3 known ","d":"prior to ","answer":"1","explain":"- Is ancient-> is of ancient","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The holograph was an instrument employed to send signals by reflecting sunlight a mirror or mirrors.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"instrument ","b":"to send ","c":"signals","d":"by reflecting sunlight ","answer":"4","explain":"- By reflecting sunlight-> by reflecting sunlight with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"In retrospect, sadness, rather anger, seems to be the overriding emotion in Langston Hughes's poetry.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"rather anger","b":"seems ","c":"overriding ","d":"emotion ","answer":"1","explain":"- Rather anger-> rather than anger","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Obsidian, an uncommon volcanic rock, polishes good and makes an attractive semiprecious stone.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"uncommon ","b":"rock","c":"polishes good ","d":"an attractive semiprecious ","answer":"3","explain":"- Polishes-> polishes well","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Business cycles have been placed the scrutiny of statisticians so that recurring patterns not apparent at first sight might be disclosed.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"placed the ","b":"statisticians","c":"so that ","d":"might ","answer":"1","explain":"- Placed the-> Placed with the","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"For a long time cotton ranked first between Alabama's crops, but today it accounts for only a fraction of the agricultural production.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"cotton ","b":"between ","c":"but ","d":"production","answer":"2","explain":"-Between->among","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}